mageplaza.com 2016-03-08

# Privacy – Mageplaza

At Mageplaza, we recognize that privacy is important and we commit to protect your privacy. This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. We assume that you accepted our policy when you sign up and use our services. 

### Information Collected

When you visit https://www.mageplaza.com , we collect your IP address and web browser information. If you want to create an account at Mageplaza, we require you provide your personal information: name, address and email address. When you purchase extensions from Mageplaza, you may need to provide us some more additional information: address, phone, company. 

### How we use your information

Our main purpose to collect your information is to provide you secure, smooth, efficient when you browse our site. We use this information to process and deliver your order, for billing purposes, for providing a more pleasant and personalized shopping experience, and for communicating with you about orders and promotional updates. You can review and edit your personal information at any time by logging in your account and go to My Account section. 

### How we use cookies

When you access our website, we may place small data files called "cookies" on your computer. This data contains information about you and it helps us to identify you if you visit multiple pages on our site during the same session, so that we don’t need to ask you for your password on each page. Once you log out your account or close your browser, this cookie expires and no longer has any effect. If you disable cookies for our site, you may still use our site, but certain benefits of your shopping experience with us may be impacted. AdWords Remarketing is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google. It connects the activity of https://www.mageplaza.com with the Adwords advertising network. You can opt out of the cookie tracking here. Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. 

### How we protect and store personal information

We commit to protect personal information. We store your information on our secured server. We use SSL for the checkout process which help you keep your billing information safe. No credit card information is saved on our system. We don’t share your personal information with any other third parties. You can always trust when doing business with Mageplaza, we always try our best to procted our customers. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Mageplaza reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact through the web site.
